本字幕由高清电台整理发布，更多高清电影请访问
https://gaoqing.fm
嘘!
Shh!
你起得真早。
You're up early.
这是什么?
What's all this?
淋浴用的。这是今天。
For the shower. It's today.
这是不是有点奇怪?
Isn't that a little strange?
什么?
What?
自己举办宝宝送礼会。
Throwing your own baby shower.
只是因为我需要完美。
It's just because I need it to be perfect.
没什么事，就是同事，卡洛琳在帮忙。
It's-it's barely anything, just people from work, and Caroline's helping.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
——什么?——什么都没有。
- What? - Nothing.
别再犯傻了。
Stop making that head.
你是说那张脸?
You mean that face?
我应该做什么表情?这张脸吗?
What face should I make? This face?
这张脸吗?我恨你。
This face? I hate you.
这张脸。
This face.
别再取笑我了!
Stop making fun of me!
你吓到我了!
You're frightening me!
过来，你。
Come here, you.
你疯了吗?停!
Are you crazy? Stop!
小心。我要打破这个。
Careful. I'm gonna break this.
你疯了。
You're crazy.
现在我动不了了。
Now I can't move.
我动不了。
I can't move.
容易得多。
Much easier.
不，不，不。
No, no, no, no.
不。
No.
我动不了了。
I can't, I can't move.
我就像一只倒立的乌龟。
I'm like a turtle on its, on its back.
你像只乌龟?
You're like a turtle?
我就像乌龟-乌龟?-在它的背上。
I'm like a turtle- - A turtle? - On its back.
嗨,乌龟。
Hi, turtle.
我的天啊!你能从那里下来吗?
Oh my god! Would you come down from there, please?
我很好。
I'm fine.
来吧。我扶你下来。
Come on. I'll help you down.
是的，搞定了。哦，在那儿。
Yeah, it, it's done. Oh, there it is.
-结束了。-谢谢。
- It's done. - Thank you.
好吧，你觉得怎么样?
Okay, what do you think?
好了。
Nice.
现在完美了。
Now it's perfect.
乔!
Jo!
这个地方太棒了!
This place is amazing!
而且离市区开车非常快。
And it was such a quick drive from the city.
我简直不敢相信。
I can't believe it.
哇!我的天啊。
Whoa! Oh my god.
好的。
Okay.
这就跟你问声好！你好!
Hi! Hello!
哇!
Wow!
乔。
Jo.
你最近怎么样?
How have you been?
好了。
There we go.
还有人想喝气泡苹果酒吗?
Anybody else want some sparkling cider?
当然,不管怎样。
Sure, whatever.
确定。
Sure.
乔。你能帮我们一下吗?
To Jo. Can you please stand up for us?
是的。来吧。
Yes. Come on.
是的,是的。
Yes, yes.
敬有史以来最好的女老板。
To the best boss lady ever.
你是一个企业家，一个领导者。
You are an entrepreneur, a leader.
你今年的读者翻了三倍。这是真的。
You tripled our readership this year. It's true.
你开了网店，搬到了州北部，还进行了疯狂的装修，顺便说一句，你还亲自回复了我们读者的每一个评论。
You launched the online shop, you moved upstate, you did this insane renovation, by the way, all the while answering every single one of our readers' comments personally.
对了，你知道的，造一个人。
And oh, by the way, you know, making a human.
如果我们不是绝对地爱你，我们都会恨你。
We would all hate you if we did not absolutely love you.
啊!
Ugh!
我很感激能成为"爱你的约瑟芬"大家庭的一员。
I feel just so grateful to be part of the "Love, Josephine" family.
哦!
Aw!
干杯!
Cheers!
-对不起，对不起-哦不!
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry. - Oh no!
我知道，我知道，我告诉自己我不会哭，但我真的会想你的。
I know, I know, I said, I told myself I was not gonna cry, but I'm really gonna miss you.
谢谢，但我哪也不去。
Oh, thanks, but I'm not going anywhere.
没有什么不同。它只是个婴儿。
Nothing's going to be any different. It's just a baby.
你知道他们到底有多大吗?
How big are they even, you know?
就像一点，一点，一点甜甜圈，一点奶油蛋糕。
It's like a little, a little, a little donut, a little brioche.
欢呼。
Cheers.
干杯,乔。
Cheers, Jo.
再见!
Bye!
你怎么看?
What do you think?
我觉得它对我来说有点小。
I think it's a little small for me.
但这是你的颜色，不是吗?
But it's your color, no?
这是我的颜色，但是，
It is my color, but,
这样好多了，不是吗?
this is better, no?
哦!
Oh!
斯宾塞，看看这件毛衣。它是完美的。
Oh, Spencer, look at this sweater. It's perfect.
大日子是什么时候?
When's the big day?
什么?
What?
婴儿。
The baby.
哦，呃，随时都有可能。
Oh, uh, any day now.
哦!
Aw!
你害怕吗?
Are you scared?
我应该害怕吗?
Should I be?
我能看看你的孩子吗?
Can I, can I see your baby?
不。
No.
你永远不会吵醒熟睡的婴儿。
You never wake a sleeping baby.
她拉住我的手。
And she stops my hand.
她拉住我的手，好像我有放射性似的。
She stops my hand like I'm, like I'm radioactive or something.
——啊。-就一小口。
- Ah. - Just a sip.
啊，我想知道会是这样。
Ah, I wonder that could be.
啊,嘘。她只是寂寞。
Ah, shh. She's just lonely.
啊,不!
Ah, no!
啊。
Ah.
妈妈,你好。
Mom, hi.
嗨,蜂蜜。我不想打扰你。
Hi, honey. I don't want to intrude.
我只是开车路过。
I was just driving by.
不，不，没关系。请进。
No, no, it's fine. Come on in.
哦，不，不，不，我不能。
Oh, no, no, no, I couldn't.
——好的。-嗨。
- Okay. - Hi.
嗨,乔。
Hi, Jo.
这就跟你问声好！
Hi!
我为你做了这些。
I made these for you.
为了满足欲望。啊。
For the cravings. Ah.
一个尝试。
Try one.
里面有什么?
What's in it?
秘方。
Secret recipe.
魔法棒。
Magic bars.
好的,很好。
Okay, fine.
花生酱，椰子，奶油糖，巧克力，樱桃碎，培根碎。
Peanut butter, coconut, butterscotch, chocolate, crushed maraschino cherries, and bacon bits.
谁知道呢?也许他们会引产。
Who knows? Maybe they'll induce labor.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
好吧。好了，我要走了。
All right. Well, I'm off.
你们好好享受你们最后的宝贵时光吧。
You two enjoy your last precious moments.
坐下，多丽丝。加入我们吧。
Sit down, Doris. Just join us.
乔，我跟你说过无数次了，叫我妈妈。
Oh, Jo, I've told you a million times, call me Mom.
说到这个，我在想，我觉得奶奶不舒服。
Speaking of which, I was thinking, Grandma doesn't feel right to me.
也许是加迪或吉迪，莫莫或咪咪，木木或咕咕，吉吉或吉哥。
Maybe Gaddy or Giddy, Momo or Mimi or Moomoo or Googoo or Gigi or Geegaw.
“等不及了……”
"Can't wait..."
哦，在里面坐好。妈妈在努力集中注意力。
Oh, settle down in there. Mommy's trying to concentrate.
神。你还好吗?
God. Are you okay?
是的。
Yeah.
我很好。
I'm fine.
只是…哦。
Just... Oh.
-天啊-有点奇怪
- Ah, Jesus - Something's weird.
你觉得…啊，是的，我认为它正在发生。
Do you think, uh... Ah, yeah, I think it's happening.
好的。
Okay.
不,请!
No, please!
好吧,亲爱的。
Okay, honey.
离我远点!
Get the fuck away from me!
五个
Five.
两个。
Two.
一个。
One.
这里一切都好吗?
Everything okay in here?
是的。
Yes.
是的，当然。
Yeah, of course.
你拉屎了吗?
Have you pooped yet?
不。
No.
你不拉屎就不能走。
You can't leave until you poop.
-谢谢。-啊，你也是。
- Thank you. - Ah, you too.
非常感谢你所做的一切。
Thank you so much for everything.
哦，你也是。
Oh, you too.
非常感谢。
Thank you so much.
哦，我们能照张相吗?
Oh, can we get a photo?
是的,是的。照片,照片。
Yeah, yeah. Photo, photo.
你能帮我们找一个吗?
Will you get one of us?
这将是她的第一张照片。
This will be her first photo.
谢谢你！非常感谢。
Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢，谢谢。
Thank you, thank you.
好吧,再见。再见。
Okay, bye. Goodbye.
等等!
Wait!
你忘了胎盘!
You forgot the placenta!
总比忘记孩子好吧?
Better than forgetting the baby, right?
我以为你想吃呢。
I thought you wanted to eat it.
婴儿吗?
The baby?
胎盘。
The placenta.
都是营养物质。
It's all nutrients.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
祝你好运。
Good luck.
啊。
Ah.
好吧，我想她进来了。
Okay, I think she's in.
你准备好了吗?是的。
You ready? Yeah.
-你还好吗?——嗯。
- You okay? - Mm-hmm.
只是，我真希望我妈妈在这。
It's just, I wish my mom were here.
好的。
Okay.
你的速度可以超过每小时两公里。
You can go faster than two kilometers per hour.
我有珍贵的货物。
Well, I have precious cargo.
我希望当父亲不会让你变成一个神经质的老太太。
I hope fatherhood is not going to turn you into a nervous old lady.
亲爱的，你为什么这么说?
Now, why would you say that, deary?
我是你的Giddy，你的Gaddy，你的Googoo，你的Gaga，你的-看路。
I'm your Giddy, your Gaddy, your Googoo, your Gaga, your- - Look at the road.
我们在哪里?
Where are we?
家
Home.
嘘。
Shh.
这上面写着他们喜欢吮吸，襁褓和荡秋千。
Well, this says they like to suck, swaddle, and swing.
我不需要什么书斯宾塞
I don't need some book, Spencer.
上面写着"销量超过一百万册，所以。"
Well, it says, "Over one million copies sold, so."
这是个陈词滥调的建议。
It's a cliche advice.
我能做到。
I can do this.
我可以做得很完美。
I can do this perfectly.
嘘。
Shh.
看。
Look.
看到了吗?
See?
好。
Well.
他妈的!
Fuck!
谁他妈大半夜的按门铃啊?
Who is ringing the doorbell in the middle of the fucking night?
我们是来排水沟的。
We're here for the gutters.
是的,是的。嗨，嗨，嗨，嗨，嗨。
Yes, Yes. Hi, hi, hi, hi, hi.
对不起，对不起，我在这里。
Sorry, sorry, I'm here.
我叫卡洛琳。我是助理。
Um, I'm Caroline. I'm the assistant.
我们会在那边安排你。
We'll set you up right over there.
就在那里。
Right over there.
嗨。
Hi.
只是来装修房子的人。
Just the guys here to work on the house.
我们会在外面。我们不会打扰你的。
We'll be outside. We won't disturb you at all.
我想我们的粉丝还在等宝宝照呢。
And hey, I think our followers are still waiting on a baby pic.
是的。
Yeah.
已经一个月了。
It's been been a month.
哦，我这就去。
Oh, uh, I'll get to it.
如果方便的话，我可以帮你。不，我没事，我没事。
I could help you if it's easier. No, I'm fine, I'm fine.
我还吃了一些
And I also had some-
-呃，乔。
- Uh, Jo.
乔，我想她又饿了。
Jo, I think she's hungry again.
大便。
Shit.
好的。
Okay.
嘘。
Shh.
好的。
Okay.
是的。
Yeah.
好姑娘。
Good girl.
好的。
Okay.
开始吧。
Here we go.
好的。
Okay.
好吧，好吧，好吧，好吧。
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
我们到了。
Here we are.
嘿。
Hey.
看。
Look.
看看她有多完美。
Look how perfect she is.
是的。
Yeah.
是你逼她的。
Well, you made her.
我们创造了她。
We made her.
好的。
Okay.
啊!斯宾塞!
Ah! Spencer!
-怎么了，乔?——Ruby !
- What's going on, jo? - Ruby!
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
当然，我完全忘了。
Of course, I completely forgot.
我几个小时前就把露比放在婴儿床上了。
I put Ruby up in her crib hours before.
我是说，乔脸上的表情…我一直都知道。你比我还害怕。
I mean, the look on Jo's face was... I knew all along. You were more scared than I was.
他对一切都很紧张。
He's nervous about everything.
我不是。
I am not.
第一次的父母。恐惧是非常非常正常的。
First-time parents. The fears are very, very normal.
如果我可以问的话，还有一个问题。
Oh, one more question, though, if I may ask.
骨头是谁的?
The bone was who's?
斯宾塞是个屠夫。手工屠夫。
Spencer's a butcher. An artisanal butcher.
我不是手艺人……我是个屠夫。
I'm not an artisanal... I'm a butcher.
你知道，放养，他主要杀的是废物。
You know, free range, He mainly killed no waste.
不管怎样，重点是我们，我们很累，所以我们想也许现在是时候，你知道，进来看看，得到一点帮助。
Anyway, the point is that we, we were very tired- - So we thought that maybe this was the time to, you know, come in and just check in and just get a little help.
不，我们不需要，我们不需要帮助，只是。-只是来看看。
No, we don't, we don't really need help, but just to- - Just to check in, you know.
只是来登记一下。
Just to check in.
她经常哭。
She cries a lot.
好消息是她看起来棒极了。
Well, the good news is she looks fantastic.
没什么好担心的。
Nothing to worry about whatsoever.
婴儿哭了。
Babies cry.
这很难，但是，你知道的，等她18岁吧。
It's tough, but, you know, wait till she's 18.
那真是地狱。
That's really hell.
啊。
Ah.
看看你!
Look at you!
你真是个可爱的小家伙?
Oh, aren't you the sweetest little thing?
她是可爱的。
She's adorable.
我觉得她看起来有点瘦。她太瘦了吗?
I think she looks a little thin. Is she too thin?
医生说她完全正常。
The doctor said she's perfectly normal.
也许她饿了。
Maybe she's hungry.
哦!
Oh!
她有很强的吸力。
She's got quite a strong suck.
嘘。
Shh.
你知道吗，人们总是说新生儿很可爱。
You know, people always say that new babies are cute.
我觉得他们看起来都像外星人。
I think they all look like ET.
我的意思是，有些人认为ET很可爱，但我只是认为他是一个令人毛骨悚然的外星人，应该呆在自己的星球上，不要打扰我们其他人。
I mean, some people thought ET was cute, but I just thought he was a creepy alien that should stay on his own planet and leave the rest of us alone.
不管怎样，如果这能安慰你的话，我理解你的感受。
Anyway, if it's any consolation, I understand how you feel.
斯宾塞爱哭。
Spencer was a crier.
哦，是吗?
Oh, he was?
噢,是的。
Oh yeah.
妈妈，别跟她唠叨个没完。她是累了。
Mom, don't talk her ear off. She's tired.
-我没事。-谢谢，亲爱的。
- I'm fine. - Thank you, dear.
我干枯。
I'm parched.
我们刚听说露比很像你。
We're just hearing about how Ruby takes after you.
妈妈，你都跟她说了些什么?
Mom, what have you been telling her about?
没什么。你是个爱哭的人，真的。
Nothing. You were a crier, you were.
-我当时还是个婴儿。——所以呢?
- I was an infant. - So?
为自己的行为负责。
Take some responsibility for your own behavior.
妈妈，你要为自己的行为负责。我确实为自己的行为负责。那你为什么要责怪你为什么要吵架?
Mom, you take some responsibility for your behavior. I did take responsibility for my behavior. So why do you blame Why are you arguing?
我告诉过你，这是。
I told you, this is.
我上楼去。
I'll go upstairs.
呃，你没事吧?
Uh, will you be okay?
你会吗?
Will you?
好。
Well.
嘘。
Shh.
没事的，鲁比。
It's okay, Ruby.
没关系。
It's okay.
嘘。
Shh.
不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ruby !
Ruby!
Ruby ?
Ruby?
婴儿。你明白吗?
Baby. You're okay?
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
哦，是的，她很好。
Oh, yeah, she's fine.
-天啊。-我没，我没看见
- Oh my God. - I didn't, I didn't see it.
看，她很好。
Oh, look, she's fine.
哦。人们都是白痴。
Oh. People are such idiots.
他们完全在街上乱飞。这是可怕的。
They completely fly down the street. It's terrifying.
我没有，我没有看到。
I didn't, I didn't see it.
我知道，我知道。太可怕了。
I know, I know. It's so scary.
所以我们才把他们绑起来。
But that's why we strap them in.
你确定她没事吗?
You sure, you sure she's fine?
是啊，她，我，看看她。她是美丽的。
Yeah, she, I- look at her. She's beautiful.
哦。
Oh.
等等，我在婴儿用品店见过你。
Wait, I, I saw you at the baby store.
没错，是的，我记得你。嗨。
That's right, yes, I do remember you. Hi.
我生了孩子。
I had the baby.
好,祝贺你。
Well, congratulations.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
太棒了。
It's great.
真的，真的，真的。
It, it really, it really is.
嘿,家伙。
Hey, guys.
嘿。
Hey.
我想让你们认识一下…天啊，我还不知道你叫什么。我很抱歉。
I want you guys to meet, um... Oh my god, I didn't even catch your name. I'm so sorry.
乔。
Jo.
这是乔，伙计们。
This is Jo, you guys.
我了解你。
I know you.
“爱,约瑟芬。”
"Love, Josephine."
法国女孩的风格。
The French girl style.
爆红网络的奶酪舒芙蕾。
The cheese souffle that broke the internet.
我的天啊!真不敢相信那是你。
Oh my god! I cannot believe that's you.
我是你的超级粉丝。你真了不起。
I'm such a fan. You're amazing.
我花了一个月时间给你做蛋奶酥。
I tried to make your souffle for like a month.
哦，很简单。这真的很简单。
Oh, it's easy. It's easy, truly.
“这很简单，真的。”
"It's easy, truly."
我知道。她很时髦，对吧?
I know. She's so chic, right?
我还没在网上看到你的孩子呢。
I haven't seen your baby online yet.
也许我错过了?
Maybe I missed it?
不，我还没有，我还没有发布。
No, I haven't, I haven't posted yet.
只是，孩子的事我不太确定。
It's just, uh, I'm not sure with the babies.
你怎么做事情?
How do you do anything?
鲁比经常哭。
Ruby cries a lot.
我知道，我知道婴儿会哭。我知道。
And I know, I know babies cry. I know that.
但有时候，这太过分了，不是吗?
But sometime it's just, it's too much, no?
你们看起来很开心，很放松，休息得很好，你们的宝宝也很安静。
And you guys look so happy and relaxed and rested, and your, your babies are, are so quiet.
他们甚至都不哭。
They don't even cry.
你的秘诀是什么?
What's your secret?
我的意思是……相信你的直觉。
I mean... Trust your instincts.
我对这身衣服不太确定。
I'm not sure about the outfit.
我觉得我们不应该去。
I don't think we should go.
来吧。
Come on.
只是晚餐而已。Ruby会没事的。
It's just dinner. Ruby will be fine.
你妈妈受不了了。
It's too much for your mother.
她养大了我，对吧?
Well, she raised me, right?
看看我现在有多棒。
Look how great I turned out.
她觉得被需要是件好事。
It's nice for her to feel needed.
再说了，我们这辈子都不能单独吃晚饭了吗?
Besides, are we never gonna have dinner again alone for the rest of our lives?
这就是我的计划?
That was my plan?
我们需要这个。
We need this.
哦，不，你是。
Oh, yes, you are.
哦，她对我笑了。
Oh, she smiled at me.
她以前笑过吗?
Has she smiled before?
你第一次笑了。
Oh, you had your first smile.
露比，你真聪明。她很聪明。
Ruby, you're so smart. She's so smart.
我错过了。
I missed it.
好吧，会有很多机会看到她微笑，皱眉，哭泣，翻白眼，对她的白痴父母表示完全的厌恶。
Okay, well, there's gonna be plenty of chances to see her smile and frown and cry and roll her eyes in complete disgust at her idiot parents.
所以。我们要迟到了。
So come. We're gonna be late.
谢谢,妈妈。
Thanks, Mom.
好的。
Okay.
牛奶在冰箱里。
The, the, the milk is in the fridge.
只要把它加热一下，一定要测试一下。
Just warm it up and make sure to test it.
我们会没事的。走吧，你们这对小情侣。
We'll be fine. Just go on, you lovebirds.
你说得对。这，这很好。
You were right. This is, this is nice.
你看到了什么?我时不时会有个好主意。
You see? Every now and again, I have a good idea.
不是很经常。大概一年一次。
Not often. Like once a year.
在闰年。
On leap years.
嘿，怎么了?
Hey, what's up?
我感觉我在消失。
I kind of feel like I'm, I'm disappearing.
嗯…好吧，这是暂时的。
Um... Well, this is temporary.
你知道吗，很快你就会回去工作，拍尿布的照片，赞助婴儿食品。
You know, pretty soon, you'll be back to work, photo shoots of diapers, baby food sponsorships.
你会以一分钟一英里的速度移动。相信我。
You'll be moving a mile a minute. Trust me.
每个人都会经历这些。
Everyone goes through this.
——真的吗?-是的。
- Really? - Yeah.
同事弗雷迪，他孩子出生后，他妻子吓坏了，她整天都在捡地毯上的线头。
You know, Freddy from work, after his kid was born, his wife got so freaked out, she just picked lint off the carpet all day.
还有吉姆，吉姆的妻子开始在网上买各种疯狂的迷你猫雕像。
Uh-huh, and Jim, Jim's wife started buying all kinds of tiny, crazy cat figurines online.
我一只小猫都没买过。
I haven't bought one tiny cat.
我知道。
I know.
因为你会是个好妈妈。
Because you're gonna be a great mom.
你的夹克上有呕吐物。
You have puke on your jacket.
我夹克上有什么?
I have what on my jacket?
你的夹克上有呕吐物。
You have puke on your jacket.
我夹克上有什么?
I have what on my jacket?
等等，我-你在做什么?
Wait, I- - What are you doing?
-给我。-不，不。
- Give it to me. - No, no.
-放一点。-控制狂
- Just put a little bit of- - Control freak.
不。我去拿。
No. I'll get it.
爱你。
Love you.
亲爱的，亲爱的露比。
Sweet, sweet Ruby.
Ruby。
Ruby.
把该死的捡起来。
Pick up the fucking.
多丽丝，快接电话!
Doris, pick up the fucking phone!
对不起，我…哇，哇，发生什么事了?
Sorry, I I... Whoa, whoa, what's happening?
监视器，莫尼-可能没什么-乔，怎么了?
The monitor, the moni- It's probably nothing- - Jo, what's going on?
但我得去看看露比。
But I just have to go check on Ruby.
把车钥匙给我。你在说什么车钥匙!
Give me the keys to the car. What are you talking The key to the car!
耶稣。
Jesus.
-我的天啊!-让开!
- Oh my god! - Out of my way!
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
乔,等等!
Jo, wait!
没关系。这是我们第一次离开她。
It's okay. It was our first time away from her.
我们会做得更好。
We'll get better at it.
你觉得是什么?
What do you think it was?
我觉得就像我妈妈说的那样。
You know, I think it's what my mom said it was.
我想她是在给露比盖毯子，然后踢翻了iPad。
I think she was, um, putting a blanket on Ruby, and she kicked over the iPad.
但我听到了耳语。
But I heard whispering.
没事，只是我妈在跟露比耳语。
Yeah, it's just my mom whispering to Ruby.
她对她说了什么?
What was she telling her?
嗯…可能是“睡个好觉”。
Um... "Sleep tight," probably.
我…我现在好了。
I'm... I'm okay now.
我知道。
I know.
我去看看露比怎么样了。
I'm just gonna go check on Ruby.
好吗?
Okay?
哦，对不起，露比。
Oh, sorry, Ruby.
没关系。
It's okay.
是妈妈。
It's just Mommy.
嘘。
Shh.
我不会再离开你了，我保证。
I won't leave you again, I promise.
好吧?我不会再离开你了。
Okay? I won't leave you again.
我再也不会离开你了。
I won't ever leave you again.
从来没有。
Never.
噢!
Ow!
你咬了我。
You bit me.
刺穿，勒死，窒息。
Impalement, strangulation, suffocation.
你确定那东西安全吗?
You sure that thing's secure?
我可不想让她承担这个责任。把她像虫子一样碾碎。
I would not want that to fall on her. Crush her like a bug.
我不喜欢这些角落的样子，而且很明显，你得把这个建筑清理一下。
I don't love the look at these corners, and obviously, you're gonna need to get this construction cleaned up.
我们很接近了。我不知道他们怎么这么久。
We are close. I dunno what's taking them so long.
完全是死亡陷阱。
Total death trap.
我知道她现在担心这些有点小，但是-开始婴儿防护永远都不嫌早。
I know she's a little young to worry about all this now, but- - Never too early to start baby proofing.
是的，她，她很先进。
Yeah, and she, she's very advanced.
她，她已经长牙了。
She, she already has teeth.
我真的希望我们的家不受她的伤害。
Well, uh, I, I really want our home to be safe from her.
对她来说很安全。
Safe for her.
是的。
Yeah.
我说什么来着?
What did I say?
没关系，我明白。
It's okay, I get it.
我们有一对双胞胎。
We had twins.
他们差点杀了我。
They almost killed me.
哇!来吧，慢性子!
Whoa! Come on, slowpoke!
哦，操，操!
Oh, fuck, fuck!
Ruby !
Ruby!
对不起，宝贝。
I'm sorry baby.
天啊，逃跑的拉尔夫!给你。
Oh my god, Runaway Ralph! Here you go.
哦，哦，谢谢。
Oh, oh, thank you.
-你还好吗?——上帝!
- You okay? - God!
我需要，我需要一支烟。
I need, I need a cigarette.
别担心。我保证，事情会变得简单很多。
Don't worry. It gets so much easier, I promise.
跑步还是孩子?
Running or the baby?
哦，可怜的家伙。鲁比还经常哭吗?
Oh, you poor thing. Is Ruby still crying a lot?
是啊，很奇怪，她不在别人面前哭，但她会哭。
Yeah, it's, it's strange, she, she doesn't do it around other people, but she, she cries.
这很经典，对吧?
It's classic, right?
你……
Do you...
你有没有觉得你的宝宝在生你的气?
Do you ever feel like you're baby's angry with you?
我是说，当我花了超过五秒钟的时间替她办事，是的。
I mean, when I take more than five seconds to do her bidding for her, yes.
她一直都很生气。
She's completely pissed all of the time.
我是说更像是惩罚你。
I mean more like punishing you.
惩罚我什么?
Punishing me for what?
我不，我不知道。
I don't, I don't know.
你知道我怎么想吗?
You know what I think?
我觉得你真的需要出去，跳舞，找回原来的自己。
I think that you really need to go out and, like, dance and get your old self back.
我们待会要一起出去喝妈妈的酒，我发誓没听起来那么糟糕。
We're actually all going out for mom drinks later, and I swear it's not as terrible as it sounds.
不，我不能。
No, I can't.
这正是让她生气的地方。
That's exactly what makes her angry.
乔，你要去哪里?
Where are you going Jo?
家  我，我得把注意力放在家里。
Home. I, I need to focus on home.
回头见。
I'll see you around.
乔。
Jo.
我很忙，卡罗琳。你看不出来吗?
I'm busy, Caroline. Can't you see?
抱歉，只是露比在哭。
Sorry, it's just that, um, Ruby's crying.
婴儿哭了。
Babies cry.
她已经哭了一个多小时了。
She's been crying for over an hour.
很好。
Fine.
我去找她，好吗?
I'll get her, okay?
很好,Ruby。
Fine, Ruby.
如果这是你想要的，我就来。
If that's what you want, I'm coming.
我不会让你赢的。
I am not going to let you win.
你听到了吗?
Do you hear me?
我不会让你赢的，露比。
I'm not gonna let you win, Ruby.
我不会让你赢的。
I'm not gonna let you win.
我不会让你赢的!
I'm not gonna let you win!
嘿。
Hey.
是什么场合?
What's the occasion?
没什么。我煮熟的。
Nothing. I cooked.
-什么事?-一个惊喜。
- What is it? - A surprise.
Ruby在哪儿?
Where's Ruby?
乔?
Jo?
乔，请等一下。来吧，等等。
Jo, wait, please. Come on, wait.
你真的认为我疯了吗?
Do you really think I'm crazy?
不，我不喜欢。我不认为你疯了。
No, I don't. I don't think you're crazy.
听着，这对我来说也很难。我他妈的累死了。
Look, this is hard on me, too. I'm fucking exhausted.
不好意思，你在自己身体里造了一个完整的人吗?
Oh, I'm sorry, but did, did you make an entire person inside your own body?
你不明白她在杀我吗?
Don't you understand that she's killing me?
我是说我想帮忙。
And I'm saying that I wanna help.
我去。我很好。
I'll go. I'm fine.
不。让我，就这一次。
No. Let me, just this once.
好的。你看你是怎么做的。
Okay. You see how you do.
走了。
Go.
好的,Ruby。
Okay, Ruby.
好吧,呃…我要出去。你和露比相处得真好。
Okay, uh... I'm going out. You're so good with Ruby.
你来照顾她一晚上。
You handle her for a night.
好吧，那你能告诉我你要去哪吗。
Okay, well, can you tell me where you're going.
出去，我说。
Out, I said.
乔，我觉得你不该出去。
Jo, I, I don't think you should go out.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
害怕和她单独在一起?
Afraid to be alone with her?
我太想和她单独在一起了。
I'm dying to be alone with her.
那么，还有什么问题呢?
So then, what's the problem, hmm?
晚饭在炉子上，但我想你已经知道了。
Dinner's on the stove, but you already know that, I think.
冰箱里有奶，露比饿了可以喝。
There is pumped milk in the fridge for when Ruby's hungry.
但喂她的时候要小心。
But be careful when you feed her.
她咬。
She bites.
Ruby。
Ruby.
你来!
You came!
是的。
Yeah.
这就跟你问声好！
Hi!
我需要出去。
I needed to get out.
你的头发看起来很可爱。
Your hair looks so cute.
它掉出来了。
It's falling out.
荷尔蒙是个婊子。
Hormones are a bitch.
Ruby。
Ruby.
乔!
Jo!
在法国，政府真的会在你生完孩子后为你的阴道修复买单吗?
Is it true that in France the government pays for you to rehab your vagina after you have a baby?
哦,是的。
Oh, yes.
是的，我们有物理治疗。
We, we have physical therapy, yes.
跟我们说说你们的育儿政策吧，因为它们太不可思议了，对吧?
Tell us about your childcare policies, because they're incredible, right?
是的，是的，我们有孩子，是的。
Yes, yeah, we have, uh, we do have childcare, yes.
-这个国家-我简直无法想象
- This country- - I can't even imagine.
嘿!这个国家就是扯淡。
Hey! This country's bullshit.
-是的。-大家注意。
- Yeah. - Everyone, note it.
我以为你们，我是说，你们看起来都很好。
I thought you all, I mean, you seem like you're doing so well.
是的，我们很痛苦。
Yeah, we're miserable.
我们是僵尸。
We are zombies.
我们非常愤怒。
We are furious.
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
说实话，真正帮我度过这一切的是吃我的胎盘。
Honestly, the thing that really helped me through all of this was eating my placenta.
我把它做成了肉酱面。
I made it into a bolognese.
你吓到她了!
You're scaring her!
我不是!
I'm not!
我忘了我的了。
I forgot mine.
让我们跳舞吧!
Let's dance!
我的还在冰箱里。
Mine is still in the freezer.
爱人摔得最惨
♪ Lovers fall the hardest ♪
♬哦♬
♪ Oh ♪
♬恋人♬
♪ Lovers ♪
♪爱的人跌倒最痛♪
♪ And lovers fall the hardest ♪
抽吸，抽吸，宝贝!
Pump and dump, baby!
是啊!哇!
Yeah! Whoo!
♬你最好跑，你最好跑
♪ You better run, you better run ♪
♬你最好快跑
♪ You better run ♪
好的。
Okay.
我不能。
I can't.
给我一分钟。请给我一分钟。
Give me a minute. Give me a minute, please.
那是什么?
What is that?
Ruby。
It's Ruby.
嗨，乔，我是雪莉。
Hey, Jo, it's Shelly.
你今晚去哪儿了?
Where were you tonight?
我以为，你会来陪妈妈喝酒。
I thought, um, you were gonna come to mom drinks.
我们真的很想你。
We really missed you.
他妈的。
Fuck.
你在哪里?
Where were you?
我在停车场睡着了。
I fell asleep in a parking lot.
是啊，我想去酒吧喝一杯，我还没进门就睡着了。
Yeah, I wanted to go to a bar to have a drink, and I, I fell asleep before I even came inside.
这么多年来我第一次睡着了。
I slept for the first time in ages.
你连个电话都不能打?
You couldn't even call?
我说了，我睡着了。
I fell asleep, like I said.
Ruby在哪儿?
Where's Ruby?
她在楼上她的婴儿床里。
She's upstairs in her crib.
她很好。别上去吵醒她。
She's fine. Don't go up there and wake her.
我们昨晚在一起过得很愉快。
We actually had a really nice night together.
好。
Good.
我为你感到高兴。
I'm happy for you.
是的。
Yeah.
好吧，终于有时间和她在一起了。
Well, it was nice to get some time with her, finally.
好吧，我不应该，我根本就不应该回来。
Okay, well, I shouldn't, I shouldn't have come back at all, then.
好吧，我不是这个意思。
Yeah, okay, that's not what I meant.
我要去工作了。总得有人知道。
I'm going to work. Someone around here has to.
这就是典型的男人。
This is typical man.
你喜欢按照自己的方式和她在一起，但一旦不方便，你就会离开。
You like to spend time with her on your terms, but then you leave whenever it becomes inconvenient.
我只是说这很好，好吗?
All I said was it was nice, okay?
是你一整晚都没来。
You're the one who left all night.
我累了，好吗?有一次我犯了个错误。
I got tired, okay? I made a mistake one time.
是吗?
Was it?
一个错误?
A mistake?
-什么意思?-我不知道。
- What do you mean? - I don't know.
你看起来很不开心。
You seem pretty unhappy.
我爱她。
I love her.
你不相信我?
You don't believe me?
别离开我，斯宾塞!
Hey, do not walk away from me, Spencer!
跟我说话!
Talk to me!
太好了。你他妈的把她吵醒了!
Great. You fucking woke her up!
啊!
Ah!
没事，露比，我听到了。停下来。
It's okay, Ruby, I heard you. Just stop.
好了。
There you go.
哦。
Oh.
对不起。
Sorry.
对不起,宝贝。
Sorry, baby.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
好消息是她在抓人。
Well, the great news is she's grabbing.
这是一个重大的里程碑。
That's a big milestone.
是时候买一个健身房了，这样她就可以拿一些不会对你身体造成伤害的东西。
It's time to get one of those activity gyms so that she can grab things that don't cause you bodily harm.
所以她没有什么问题?
So there's nothing wrong w-with her?
她很好。
She's perfectly fine.
你肯定看到了，但她有牙齿。
Uh, I'm sure you saw, but she has teeth.
现在说这个有点早，但每个宝宝都不一样。
Well, it's a little early for that, but all babies are different.
她她在你看来不生气吗?
And she she doesn't seem angry to you?
关于什么?
What about?
不，没什么，我只是…如果她失望了，我能理解。
No, nothing, I just, I mean... I would understand if she's disappointed.
在什么?她是个婴儿。
In what? She's a baby.
她还没到失望的年龄。
She's not old enough to be disappointed.
嗯…
Um...
我马上就回来。
I'm gonna be right back.
等等，你要去哪?
Wait, w-where are you going?
结果她要去打针了。
Turns out she's due for some shots.
这只需要一分钟。
This will only take a minute.
“你的宝宝想告诉你什么?”
"What is your baby trying to tell you?"
哦，她完全失去理智了。
Oh, she's completely lost her marbles.
我担心她会。
I worry that she might.
嘿，没事，没事。嘘。
Hey, it's okay, it's okay. Shh.
嘿，嘿，你不能走!
Hey, hey, you can't leave!
现在，现在不是时候，真的。我们会回来的。
Uh, it's, it's not a good time, really. We'll come back.
我错了。
I was wrong.
哇，哇，你在这里做什么?
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing here?
-什么都说。——耶稣。
- About everything. - Jesus.
啊，对不起。
Ah, I'm sorry.
——嘘。-她没有生我的气。
- Shh. - She's not angry with me.
她当然不生气。她不是。
Of course she's not angry. She's not.
这简直是疯了。她没有什么问题。
That was completely insane. There's nothing wrong with her.
她，她不是想伤害我。
She's, she's not trying to hurt me.
-是的。-她，她想告诉我一些事
- Yeah. - She, she's trying to tell me something.
理解宝宝的暗示是有道理的。
It makes sense, you know, understanding your baby's cues.
哭啊，抓啊。
The, the, the crying, the grabbing.
她拼命地想和我们交流，而她唯一能。-那她想和我们交流什么?
She's trying desperately to communicate with us, and the only way she can- - So what is she trying to communicate?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我不知道。Uhhuh吗?
I don't know. Uhhuh?
我觉得她可能是想警告我们。
I think she, she may be trying to warn us.
医生怎么说?
What did the doctor say?
我没有告诉他这件事。他只会认为我疯了。
I didn't tell him about this. He'll just think I'm crazy.
我送你回家，乔。
Yeah, I'm gonna take you home, Jo.
我不希望她在这里，等我们回来，也许我们能解决这个问题，也许你也能休息一下，好吗?
Uh, I don't want her here, and, uh, when we, when we get back, maybe we can figure this out, and maybe you can get a little rest, hmm?
我不需要休息。
I don't need to rest.
当你筋疲力尽的时候，你是想不出答案的。
Well, you can't figure this out when you're exhausted.
我不是。
I'm not.
嘿，看着我。
Hey, look at me.
我爱你。
I love you.
我也爱你。
I love you too.
好的。
Okay.
嘘，嘘，嘘。
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
没关系。好姑娘。
It's okay. Good girl.
好姑娘。
Good girl.
嗨。
Hi.
我想给你带点茶。
I thought I would bring you some tea.
斯宾塞不该打扰你的，真的
Spencer shouldn't have bothered you, really.
我可以自己照顾鲁比。
I can take care of Ruby myself.
露比不是唯一需要照顾的人。
Ruby isn't the only one who needs taking care of.
谢谢。
Thanks.
哦，那是经典。
Oh, that's a classic.
是啊，我以为我不需要这些书，但是-我知道。
Yeah, I, I didn't think I'd need these books, but- - I know.
这是地狱。
It's hell.
什么?
What?
我跟你说过斯宾塞小时候的事。
Well, I told you about when Spencer was a baby.
是的。你说他爱哭。
Yes. You said he was a crier.
哦，比那糟多了。
Oh, much worse than that.
这是我年轻的时候。男人们什么也没做。
You know, this was back in my day. Men didn't do anything.
我孤身一人，每个人都在说，我是不是很幸福，我的孩子难道不是一个奇迹吗，我感到很内疚，因为我当然爱他，但同时，
I was all alone, and everybody kept saying, wasn't I so happy, and wasn't my baby a miraculous thing, and I, I felt so guilty because of course I loved him, but also,
我恨他。
I hated him.
我会梦见所有可能发生在他身上的可怕的事情，起初我以为这是因为我害怕。
I would dream about all the terrible things that could happen to him, and at first I thought it was because I was scared.
我是说，所有的妈妈都很害怕。
I mean, all moms are scared.
但后来我意识到
But then I realized
我许了个愿。
I Wished for it.
我做到了。
I did.
一天晚上，斯宾塞的父亲又出差了，斯宾塞哭个不停，我试了各种方法，但都没用。
And one night, Spencer's father was on another business trip, and Spencer was crying and crying, and I tried everything, but nothing worked.
我很热。
And I was hot.
夏天。半夜的时候，外面很黑。
Summer. It was dark outside, middle of the night.
我记得我只是，
And I, I remember I just,
我向上帝祈祷，希望有人能把这个孩子从我身边带走，这样我就能变回以前的我。
I prayed to God for someone to come and just take this baby away from me so that I could go back to being who I was before.
但我也知道，我知道那是不可能的。
But also, I knew, I knew that wasn't gonna happen.
我被困住了。
I was, I was trapped.
我把斯宾塞放在他的婴儿床上，他一直哭啊哭啊哭，就像锤子一样，在我脑子里，然后我，我下楼去厨房拿了我们最锋利的刀。
I put Spencer in his crib, and he was crying and crying and crying and crying, like a hammer, like, um, in my head, and I, I went down into the kitchen and I got our sharpest knife.
自杀?
To kill yourself?
杀了他。
To kill him.
我回到楼上，他就。-别说了。
I went back upstairs, and he was just- - Stop.
停下来。
Just stop.
显然，我恢复理智了。
Well, obviously, I came to my senses.
我什么都没做。
I mean, I didn't do anything.
你必须停下来。
You have to stop.
是的，这就是问题所在。
Yes, and that's the problem.
我们不能谈这些事，甚至不能对彼此说。
We can't talk about these things, not even to each other.
我们不能承认。我们甚至不能看它。
We can't admit it. We can't even look at it.
所以
And so
它变得更强大。
it grows stronger.
Ruby。
Ruby.
嘿，嘿，嗯，我妈妈在这过夜，所以你可以…
Hey, hey, um, my mom's staying over, so you can...
瞧。
Voila.
我没那么饿。
I'm not that hungry.
是牛角面包，但我们得让你吃饱。
Well, it's croissant, but we have to keep you fed.
你朋友来过了，谢莉。
Oh, and your friend dropped by, Shelly.
她扔下一块大蛋糕。
She dropped off a loaf cake.
你看起来休息得好多了。
You're looking more rested already.
我没听见露比在夜里醒来。
I didn't hear Ruby wake up in the night.
我猜她睡过头了。
I guess she slept through.
做得好，鲁比!
Good job, Ruby!
你没听到她说的话吧?
You didn't hear her, did you?
一点动静也没有。
Not a a peep.
当然，我在楼下沙发上，所以。
Of course, I'm downstairs on the sofa, so.
我并不是在抱怨。
Not that I'm complaining.
我只是后背有点刺痛。
I just get a little twinge in my back.
我知道客房还没装修好，但我想要个结实点的床垫。
I know the guest room isn't finished, but I would love a firmer mattress.
我在想我和斯宾塞约会的第一个晚上你帮了我多大的忙。
I was thinking how helpful you've been that first night Spencer and I went out.
我知道，你很担心。
I know, you were so worried.
那些魔法棒里有什么?
What was in those magic bars?
那天晚上我就分娩了。
I went into labor at the very night.
我希望你不会认为。-我会怎么想?就是个典型的紧张妈妈，不是吗?
I hope you don't think- - Oh, what would I think? Just a typical nervous mom, no?
我向你保证，没什么好担心的。
I promise you, there's absolutely nothing to worry about.
我一直保持警惕。
I keep a very watchful eye.
我也是。
So do I.
乔，排水沟终于清理完了，你想去看看吗。
Jo, the guys are finally done with the gutters, if you wanna go give it a quick look.
我来照看鲁比。
I'll watch Ruby.
我两分钟后回来。
I'll be back in two minutes.
别带她离开秋千。
Don't take her out of the swing.
你想让我上去吗?
Do you want me to go up there?
不不不，我只是-天啊!——对不起。
No, no, no, I just- Oh my god! - Sorry.
那完全是个意外。
That was a complete accident.
你们这些白痴怎么了?
What is wrong with you idiots?
一切都好吗?
Is everything okay?
一切都很好。我就带露比出去走走。
All is well. I'll just take Ruby out for a walk.
没关系。
It's okay.
让她走。
Let her go.
我是斯宾塞。
Hey, this is Spencer.
我现在没法让他接电话。
I can't make him on the phone right now.
雪莱。
Shelly.
雪莉!
Shelly!
哦,上帝。
Oh god.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
这是怎么回事?
What is going on?
关上，把门关上。赶快关上。
Just close, close the door. Close it quickly.
他们可能在跟踪我。
They may be following me.
哦,他妈的。大便。
Oh fuck. Shit.
是因为斯宾塞吗?狗屎!
Is this about Spencer? Shit!
他发现了吗?
Did he find out?
乔，拜托告诉我你没告诉他。
Jo, please tell me you didn't tell him.
告诉他什么?
Tell him what?
你是醉得不记得了，还是这事无关紧要?
Were you too drunk to remember, or was it just that insignificant?
我以为那是个梦。
I thought that was a dream.
这不是梦吗?
It was not a dream?
一场梦吗?我该把这当成是恭维吗?
A dream? Should I be taking that as a compliment?
我不停地给你发短信，还给你烤了个蛋糕，给你留了张卡片，而你就像幽灵一样把我消失了。
I texted you and texted you, and then I baked you a loaf cake and I leave you a card, and you just completely ghosted me.
-我很抱歉，我没有-你知道吗，我懂了，因为我结婚了
- I'm sorry, I didn't- - And it's like, you know what, I get it, because I'm married.
我也不想因为这件事毁了我的生活。
I don't wanna blow up my life over this, either.
但你是法国人。我以为我们可以像法国人一样。
But you're French. I thought we could be French about it.
这有什么大不了的?他妈的!
Like, what's the big fucking deal? Fuck!
我现在真的很脆弱因为我的性取向和女人味，我一直觉得自己糟透了，你这么对我让我感觉更糟，
I'm just in a really, like, vulnerable place right now with my sexuality and my femininity, and I feel like fucking shit all the time, and you doing that to me makes me feel even worse,
我甚至找不到一个可以倾诉我现在感受的人。
and I don't even have anyone I can talk to about how I'm feeling right now.
我真的很想谈谈这件事。我真的很抱歉。
I do really wanna talk about this. I really apologize.
但我得打个非常非常快的电话。
But I need to make a quick, quick phone call.
严重吗?安静点，我的孩子睡着了。
Seriously? Just be quiet, because my baby's asleep.
我是斯宾塞。
Hey, this is Spencer.
我现在不方便接电话，请在哔的一声后留言。
I can't make it to the phone right now, so leave your message after the beep.
嘿，是我。我需要和你谈谈。
Hey, it's me. I need to talk to you.
露比有危险。我有危险。
R- Ruby is in danger. I am in danger.
求你了，让大家都走吧，我们好好谈谈。
Please just, just send everyone away, and let us talk.
我能看看吗?
Can I see?
不。
No.
你的秘诀是什么?
What's your secret?
只是你的直觉。
Just your instincts.
没有婴儿。
There were no babies.
从来没有孩子。
There were never any babies.
♬你的小女孩，你的小女孩♬
♪ Your little girl, your little girl ♪
你在里面做什么?
What are you doing in there?
什么都没有。
Nothing.
没什么，我只是…把我的孩子还给我。
Nothing, I just... Just give me my baby.
天啊，她太完美了。
Oh my god, she's so perfect.
她真是个完美的小天使，乔。
She's really just a perfect little angel, Jo.
第一天在婴儿店你为什么要来找我?
Why did you come up to me that first day at the baby store?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我是个好目标，对吧?
I was a good target, huh?
显然不知道我要做什么。
Clearly had no idea what I was in for.
现在，把她还给我。
Now, you give her back to me.
乔，说实话吧。
Jo, let's be honest.
她毁了你的生活。
She's ruining your life.
把她还给我。
Give her back to me.
不。
No.
-把她还给我——没有。
- Give her back to me. - No.
你必须小心。你不会想伤害她的。
And you have to be careful. You don't wanna break her.
把我的孩子还给我。
Give me my baby.
——不!-给我-该死!
- No! - Give me- Ow, shit!
她他妈的咬了我!
She fucking bit me!
做得好，鲁比。好工作。
Good job, Ruby. Good job.
你做到了。
You did it.
我们做到了。
We did it.
我不会让他们带走你的。
I won't let them take you.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
-我暂时还好。——是吗?
- I'm okay, for now. - Yeah?
好的，感谢上帝。我很担心。
Okay, thank God. I was so worried.
-我们时间不多了。-好吧，没关系。
- We don't have much time. - Okay, that's okay.
我很担心，我以为你。-他们想要露比。
I was so worried, I thought that you- - They want Ruby.
-谁要她。-他们要，他们要她，我不知道为什么
- Who wants her. - They want, they want her, I don't know what for.
好吧，我不明白。
Okay, I don't understand.
我无法向你解释，但你必须相信我。
I can't explain you, but you have to trust me.
好吧,好吧。谁想要鲁比?
Okay, okay. Who wants Ruby?
你还穿着围裙?
You're still wearing your apron?
是啊，你留言说你有危险，所以我尽快赶来了。
Yeah, well, your message said you were in danger, so I came as fast as I could.
她也没事，所以别再偷偷摸摸去不该去的地方了。
And she's okay, so no more sneaking around where you don't belong.
待在这里。我上楼去梳洗一下。
Stay here. I'm gonna go upstairs and get cleaned up.
你就待在这里
You're gonna stay right here,
等我回来的时候，我们可以谈谈，好吗?
and then, when I come back down, we can talk, okay, mm-hmm?
你没事吧?
You gonna be okay?
是的,当然。
Yes, sure.
好。
Good.
待在这里。
Stay here.
哦!
Oh!
对不起，乔。
I'm sorry, Jo.
我很抱歉闯进来。
I'm so sorry to barge in.
我一路开车回家，发现我忘了带钥匙。
I drove all the way home and realized that I forgot my keys.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
不，我，我很好。
No, I'm, uh, I'm fine.
我很好。我，我正准备做晚饭。
I'm fine. I was, uh, I was just about to make dinner.
太好了，我饿死了。来，我看着她。
Oh, good, I'm starved. Here, I'll watch her.
在这里。加油，加油。
Here. Come on, little on.
来咕咕吧。
Come to Googoo.
你好。她长这么大了。
Hi. She's getting so big.
她要养这么大的女儿了。
She's getting such a big girl.
这是我吃过的最好吃的肉酱面。
This is the best bolognese I have ever had.
好吧，你得把秘方给她。
Yeah, well, you'll have to give her the recipe.
哦，很简单。
Oh, it's pretty simple.
你要做的就是全身心投入。
All you have to do is throw yourself into it.
乔，我们得谈谈。
Jo, we, uh, we need to talk.
你不喜欢吗?
You don't like it?
你需要休息。
You need a rest.
更长的休息时间。
A longer rest.
也许几周后。
Maybe a few weeks away.
一些专业的帮助。
Some professional help.
你可以服用一些药物，露比会没事的。
There's medications you can take and, uh, yeah, Ruby will be fine.
妈妈愿意帮忙。
Mom's offered to help.
的确，我一直在努力，我没有意识到，在这个国家，没有人帮助母亲。
It's true that I, I've been really struggling and I, I didn't realize, nobody helps mothers in this country.
我们会给你提供你需要的帮助。
We're gonna get you the help you need.
专业人士来了。
Professionals are coming.
他们正在来接你的路上-没有露比吗?
They're on their way now to meet you and take you- - Without Ruby?
你自己也说过。
You said it yourself.
露比有危险。
Ruby's in danger.
他们会带你去一个可以休息的地方。
So they're gonna take you to a place you can rest.
我们会把你的东西都拿来。
We'll bring all your things.
我可以……
Can I...
至少让我跟她说声再见吧?
Can I at least say goodbye to her?
当然。
Of course.
露比，跟妈妈说再见。
Ruby, say goodbye to Mommy.
跟妈妈说再见。
Say bye to Mommy.
我会想你的。
I'm gonna miss you.
不要动!
Don't move!
只是不喜欢。
Just don't.
你以为你能轻易摆脱我吗?
You think you can get rid of me so easily?
你想让我相信我疯了，但我知道你在做什么。
You want me to believe that I'm crazy, but I know what you're doing.
我知道真相。
I know the truth.
我知道。
I know.
母亲的直觉从不说谎。
A mother's instincts never lie.
你怎么能这样?你怎么能这样对我们?
How could you? How could you do this to us?
你自己的女儿。
Your own daughter.
我恨你。
I hate you.
我不知道这是什么。
I don't know what this is.
我不知道你找她做什么。
I don't know what you want her for.
但我保证，你永远得不到她。
But I promise this, you will never have her.
我永远，永远不会让她走。从来没有。
I will never, never let her go. Never.
大便。
Shit.
乔，开门!他妈的把门打开!
Jo, open the door! Open the fucking door!
乔，开门!
Jo, open the door!
开门!
Open the door!
乔!加油，加油!
Jo! Come on, come on!
别这样，乔!
Don't fucking do this, Jo!
乔，开门!
Jo, open the door!
加油，加油!
Come on, come on!
别这样，乔!
Don't fucking do this, Jo!
停下该死的车，乔!
Stop the fucking car, Jo!
停车，他妈的停车!停!
Stop, stop the fucking car! Stop!
乔!
Jo!
来吧!
Come on!
停车。来吧!
Stop the car. Come on!
乔!
Jo!
嘘。没事的，鲁比。
Shh. It's okay, Ruby.
没关系，没关系。
It's, it's okay.
没事的，鲁比。
It's okay, Ruby.
嘘。
Shh.
没事的，鲁比。
It's okay, Ruby.
嘘。
Shh.
♬啦啦啦啦啦♬
♪ La la la la la ♪
♬啦啦啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦♬
♪ La la la la la, la la la la la ♪
我们好了。
We're okay.
Ruby ?
Ruby?
鲁比在哪里?
Where is Ruby?
Ruby。
Ruby.
Ruby ?
Ruby?
鲁比在哪里?
Where is Ruby?
她是好的。
She's okay.
你现在就好，好吗?
You just get well now, okay?
我以为……-我知道。-我以为她…我以为你，你不是…我也不知道了。嘘。
I thought... - I know. - I thought she was... I thought that you were, you were n-not... I don't know anymore. Shh.
你好好休息，好吗?
You just rest up, okay?
幻觉，精神病发作?
The visions, psychotic episodes?
一去不复返了。
Gone.
幻听?
Auditory hallucinations?
你脑袋里的哭声?
The crying in your head?
不。
No.
偏执?阴谋论?
Paranoia? Conspiracy theories?
我想我们要去公园。
I think we're gonna go to the park.
我们可以一起去公园。
We can all go to the park.
怪物吗?
Monsters?
只有我。
Only me.
这一切似乎都是那么真实。
It all seemed so real.
它是真实的。
It is real.
产后是真实的。
Postpartum is real.
这不是你的错。
And it's not your fault.
如果他们回来了呢?
And if they come back?
愿景?
The visions?
我知道你很害怕。
I know you're afraid.
慢慢来。
Just take it moment by moment.
你熬过了第一个晚上，然后是下一个晚上，然后就变得容易了。
You get through the first night, and then the next, and then it gets easier.
准备好了。
Ready.
好的。
Okay.
我来接。
I'll get this.
等着看露比吧。
Wait till you see Ruby.
她用她的小屁股在地板上滑来滑去。
She's scooting across the floor on her little bum bum.
还没说话，但她一直在喋喋不休。
And no words yet, but she's just babbling away.
最后，她能睡个安稳觉，这显然让她松了一口气。
And finally, she is sleeping through the night, which was such a relief, obviously.
谢谢。
Thanks.
为了什么?
For what?
Ruby。
Ruby.
我真不知道没有你我们该怎么办。
I, I don't know what we would've done without you.
没什么。
It's nothing.
我母亲去世了;我当时只是个婴儿。
My mother died; I was, I was only a baby.
我知道。
I know.
所以我不能叫你妈妈。
So I couldn't call you Mom.
但我还是做不到。
And I still can't.
没关系。
It's okay.
去做吧。
Go ahead.
没关系。
It's all right.
我得去收拾行李了。
Uh, I have to go unpack.
露比应该熬过今晚。
Ruby should go through the night.
我明早会陪她的。
I'll spend some time with her in the morning.
她爱你。
She loves you.
如何?
How?
在我做了这么多之后?
After all I've done?
你是她妈妈。
You're her mother.
你知道吗，当警察到达事故现场时，你几乎没有意识。
You know, when the police arrived at the scene of the accident, you were barely conscious.
汽车被压碎了。
Car was crushed.
没人知道你是怎么爬出来的，但你还是爬出了座位。
Nobody knows how, but somehow, you managed to crawl out of your seat.
你爬回露比身边。
You crawled back to Ruby.
当他们找到你的时候
And when they found you,
你在掩护她，保护她。
you were covering her, protecting her.
我很害怕。
I'm scared.
然后……
Then...
让我们熬过今晚。
Let's just get through tonight.
嘿。
Hey.
我来了，露比。
I'm coming, Ruby.
Ruby。
Ruby.
一切都会没事的。
Everything's gonna be okay.
嘘。
Shh.
没事的，鲁比。
It's okay, Ruby.
好吧。
All right.
嘘。
Shh.
好吧。嘘。
All right. Shh.
一切都会没事的。
Everything's gonna be okay.
这就是你想要的。
That's what you wanted.
给我一分钟给你做瓶酒。
Just give me one minute to make your bottle.
没事，就一会儿，露比。
Yeah, it will just be a minute, Ruby.
一切都会好起来的，露比。
Everything is gonna be okay, Ruby.
♬啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦
♪ La la la, la la la la la la ♪
♬啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦♬
♪ La la la, la la la la la ♪
请Ruby。
Please, Ruby.
请。你可以做到的。
Please. You can do this.
是的，露比可以有耐心。
Yeah, Ruby can be patient.
是的。
Yeah.
闭嘴，鲁比!
Shut up, Ruby!
别哭了。
You just stop your crying.
你他妈的别哭了!
You stop fucking crying!
让它停下来。
Make it stop.
嘿!
Hey!
Ruby !
Ruby!
嘿!
Hey!
停!
Stop!
Ruby !
Ruby!
不!
No!
你不能拥有她。
You can't have her.
你是个糟糕的母亲。
You're a terrible mother.
她不想让你做她妈妈。
She doesn't want you as her mother.
我不怕你。
I'm not afraid of you.
我不害怕
I'm not afraid.
我不是。
I'm not.
过来。
Come here.